# **Heesoo Park**

# Full Stack Web developer



A versatile developer who is well-versed in front-end, back-end as well as interactive web design. Able to work efficiently with strong organizational skills and attention to detail based on years of experience as a marketing specialist. Passionate about learning and able to adopt new skills quickly.

#### **SKILLS**

Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL

Framework & Library: React.js, Node.js, Express, EJS, Socket.l.O, jQuery, ajax, React-redux

Database & System: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Git

**Design Tool :** Figma, Adobe Illustrator **Test :** Jest, Cypress, Mocha, Chai

#### **PROJECTS**

### Lighthouse-town

- Developed a gamification chat app that allows users to chat and move their avatars in real-time
- Integrated Socket.I.O library which allows bidirectional Websocket connection for chatting and sharing all avatars' locations in real-time
- Utilized Javascript class and instance for creating avatars and created React.js reusable components for each chat room
- Tech stack: React.js | Node.js | Express | HTML Canvas | Socket.I.O | PostgreSQL | Heroku

#### **Pick The Dishes**

- Developed a food ordering and order management app for a restaurant with an SMS notification function
- Structured PostgreSQL database, designed RESTful API to get food data and store order data to the database and utilized third-party API to implement an SMS notification function
- Tech stack: Node.js | Express | EJS | PostgreSQL | Twilio API | Axios | ajax | Sass | Heroku

#### **Shoes Market**

- A front-end e-commerce site for shoe shopping with a responsive design
- Utilized Redux to manage the number of items in the cart and leveraged localStorage to store recently viewed items
- Tech stack: React.js | Redux | React-router | CSS

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Volunteer in a local business BIONE LIFE LTD. BC, Canada

- Created an e-commerce website by using Shopify and designed marketing design content with Figma **Early Childhood Educator** – BC, Canada, 2020.02 - 2022.01

Planned and implemented class lectures and organized class events, communicating with parents

**Marketing Specialist and Finance Advisor** - National Agricultural Cooperative Federations, South Korea 2014.01 - 2019.05

- Organized marketing strategies and events under tight deadlines which contributed the corporation to be placed 1st among 4,000 federations

#### **EDUCATION**

**Diploma of Web Development** Lighthouse Labs 2022.04 - 2022.06 **Bachelor of Business Administration** Ajou University 2009.0 - 2014.02